Instead I'll tell you how we can create an extension that will look similar to click to remove
elements and hide it. How it works basically allows us to hide or remove specific elements that
bothers us. It's especially useful for me, for example if I'm recording some stuff on my website,
maybe I want to hide specific stuff like maybe my earnings, maybe my credential, and if I
have the top right corner if it's displayed, or if I record my jimohibox, maybe I want to hide
some of the specific elements too. We get to add additional layer of security and privacy.
So as you can see it's installed, we'll be able to press hide that and then
then I will be hidden after that. So I'll use hacker tab and I will use one of the links that
are there just to test it out. So the first is just some mustard on and some links and I can
press hide that basically. And it disappeared immediately because it detected the element that
we pressed. This is the login. I can press hide that and it easily removed the part of the website
that actually hovered. Another one is click to remove element. It's pretty great because it allows
us to as well save the elements that are hidden, we just press it and now we see like a picker
when you can just try to adapt which element should be hidden and that allows us in this place
all of the elements that are below it, even shortcut for that color shift plus x and you can
remember by default which can be saved, especially if we revisit that page that we previously
adjusted for that. So now if I type it and hide something as you can see it disappeared
and basically it saved the default and the remove element is just sign in banner. So we don't want
to see the sign in banner visible on mustard on and now when I refresh our website as you can see
it has been saved. So this element obviously exists on the server side but we as a client do not
see it because we hit it with that extension. I will create a new folder now and just for testing
purposes I will just use it and I have to extension that I show because we can obviously preview
the resource code but it's just for education purposes. I don't want to copy these tools but probably
just get some of the functionality that we will use in our own extension for non-commercial uses.
So now we have to add a folder and we can even just redirect ourselves to any specific thing.
So now I can use a hideout by looking at the extension to make a Chrome extension and in this folder.
So the hideout is just my name but click the remove element
will be the project that actually I am using as an empty file and now when I have it let me check
it's best to reverse. Sometimes you can use even a chat GPT to extract you how you can prompt
out your way to create some of the tools. So now we just create a new tool because
I will just use cars creation so it will be user and now I will just use it as a reference. So
it will just try to create all of the tools and align the extension and recreate it for our purposes.
Last month and the five to do is create my first JSON and create it.
I can't escape to handle element hiding from hiding a right click so we want to have it as a
like task when we use the right mouse pattern and other related to self-postivity and restore
element. So it was returned but there was an error. So it was allowed to create a new path icon
sometimes it has to be done only because you don't have an icon we have to edit manually it can
be used by chat GPT and we can create our own ones just for testing purposes it can be even a
blank picture because it's just a requirement to even test it out in a Chrome extension because
it should display some of the icon that you have added to your content directory.
And I will remove it and use it because it started to create
like different version of that extension I don't want it I just want to get the functionality
and recreation in the new Chrome extension. So it displayed some of the issues because I
realized there was some problem but now it's creating in the new folder and we see
and we see additional files that are being added to the local of directory. All right it has been
finished so now I have another extension. So we use extension panel, manage extension and now we use
load and packed. I'll go to the folder that I have set up in the Chrome extension and it's obviously
course creation. So this one and we have to specify and see if we can edit. All right we have
clicked remove element it has been added I refreshed and now we can pick it up to our web browser.
It's here remove the element but it's just as a pin set maybe I will go to another website
and try to look if we actually can hide something. I was hacking news and one of the news this one
is a BBC all right having it's great and now I click to remove element this is our element
a press remove element and the local BBC has disappeared as well for register signing we can
remove the element it remove that but not entirely but you can go one by one and this is like very
easy and extension but very actually nice especially want to hide some of the parts of the website
that are not useful for us.